All right I'm back, I'm just doing a little fast clean up.
You see we got all of our beautiful shrimp here breaded with the crabmeat stuffing, look at how wonderful.
Here's the trick, you take your Parmesan cheese, fresh Parmesan cheese.
Go out and get fresh.
Go over each one, nice.
They will brown it, it'll look beautiful in the oven.
I'm telling you that's how you're going to know when they're done.
When they're nice and brown you take them out and you got a beautiful dinner.
Make some asparagus like I said.
Open up a bottle of nice white wine.
Guys do this for your girls; I'm telling you'll be writing me.
I mean, let's talk a little bit about prep time.
Prep time, I'm not really sure it's probably about 25 minutes.
I mean come on, isn't 25 minutes worth it to your girls?
Do something nice for your ladies; they're going to love you for it.
I mean I know I'm no Rachel Ray, she does them 30-minute meals but she inspires me, and I think we have a lot in common.
So with that said, I know she's a better cook, but maybe one day I will get to cook for her who knows, I could dream.
Put these in the oven, 350 right in the middle.
We'll come back when they're done.
We're going to eat it, we're going to open up some wine, and we're going to tell you storage, how much it costs.